{
  "profileId": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c7",
  "selectedIndustries": ["649b5f09fe840a75193787cb"],
  "selectedInterests": [],
  "responses": [
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b3db2d50f2c4652f63bc0",
      "response": "working with machines",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117190e",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117190f",
      "response": "analytical",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171910",
      "response": "independently",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171911",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171912",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171913",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171914",
      "response": "fast paced",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171915",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171916",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171917",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171918",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171919",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191a",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191b",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191c",
      "response": "no",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191d",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191e",
      "response": "not important",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191f",
      "response": "hybrid",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    },
    {
      "user": "64b16ff9746c9b7bcdeb29c5",
      "question": "64a86abdd8f3617c13237c93",
      "response": "yes",
      "createdBy": "Petaviv Lukaat",
      "lastModifiedBy": "Petaviv Lukaat"
    }
  ]
}
